(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Don't bother.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)I'll just go sit in a hole in the ground
so I'm no trouble when I die.
(Howard:)Stop it, Ma.
(Howard:)I'm sure I can get Bernie to come around.
I knew it! I knew she was behind this.
You listen to me, if you wanna be a man
you can't let a woman tell you what to do.
(Howard:)Okay, okay.
(Dimitri:)I can't believe these people
won the Cold War.
(Howard:)Now, can we please change the subject?
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Fine. Explain why you've been gone so long
and I haven't gotten a single letter.
Not even a lousy postcard!
(Leonard:)You know,
I'm growing to like American football.
- Yeah, it's fun, isn't it?
- Well...
(Raj:)...it's not the balls-to-the-wall action
of badminton or cricket, but hey...
(Raj:)...what is?